<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reid Mitchell</title><link>https://reidmit.com/</link><description>Recent content on Reid Mitchell</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://reidmit.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A2B</title><link>https://reidmit.com/projects/a2b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reidmit.com/projects/a2b/</guid><description>With A2B, I designed the user experience and user interface for a travel app that would eliminate the frustrating or painful parts of travel planning. As the sole designer on the project, I did the research, prototyping, testing, and final wireframes over the course of three weeks.
The idea I started with a hypothesis. People love to dream of taking vacations. We have fun coming up with what these trips might look like: where we&amp;rsquo;ll go, what we&amp;rsquo;ll eat, what we&amp;rsquo;ll do.</description></item><item><title>Pivotal UI</title><link>https://reidmit.com/projects/pivotal-ui/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reidmit.com/projects/pivotal-ui/</guid><description>For the first year and a half of my job at Pivotal, I worked on the team that maintained Pivotal UI, the company&amp;rsquo;s design system and component library.
The library is open source, written in React and CSS, and can be found on GitHub. The documentation, plus examples of the components in use, can be found in our style guide.
This was such a fun project to work on, and I cannot overstate how much I learned.</description></item><item><title>Asyncronous coffee-making with JavaScript</title><link>https://reidmit.com/writing/asynchronous-coffee-making-with-javascript/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 12:23:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reidmit.com/writing/asynchronous-coffee-making-with-javascript/</guid><description>Asynchronous programming comes up a lot when you hear about JavaScript. You may have heard about callbacks, promises, or async/await. These were things that took me a long time to grasp. Even well into writing JavaScript every day at my job, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t fully comfortable with my understanding. In this post, I want to share how I&amp;rsquo;ve learned to think about asynchronous programming: what it means, why it&amp;rsquo;s useful, and how it&amp;rsquo;s implemented in JavaScript.</description></item><item><title>Redraw</title><link>https://reidmit.com/projects/redraw/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reidmit.com/projects/redraw/</guid><description>Redraw is a tool for making pixel art. Try it out!
The code is all on GitHub. It&amp;rsquo;s written in React and uses the HTML5 canvas for drawing.
I started this project during a vacation at home. I was getting nostalgic for all the time I used to spend making drawings in MS Paint. I no longer have a Windows computer, so I went looking for a browser-based replacement. I found JsPaint, which is an amazing recreation of the old version of Paint that I loved.</description></item><item><title>Wrapping your head around recursion</title><link>https://reidmit.com/writing/wrapping-your-head-around-recursion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 05:17:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reidmit.com/writing/wrapping-your-head-around-recursion/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s start with an analogy.
Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re standing in a long line of people waiting for something on a very foggy day. It&amp;rsquo;s so foggy that nobody in line can see further than one person ahead of them and one person behind them. You certainly can&amp;rsquo;t see the beginning of the line. But you&amp;rsquo;re growing impatient, so you would like to know your position in the line. Are you 5thor 500th?</description></item><item><title>How I built this site</title><link>https://reidmit.com/writing/how-i-built-this-site/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 15:21:51 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://reidmit.com/writing/how-i-built-this-site/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m fascinated by the different technologies, languages, and methods people use to build websites. When I see a website I admire, I often spend time digging to see how it was built. So, I wanted to share the details behind how this site is made.
There are tons of great options out there for this kind of thing, all with different strengths: Wordpress, Jekyll, Hexo, Gatsby, to name just a few.</description></item><item><title>A new website (finally!)</title><link>https://reidmit.com/writing/a-new-website/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 05:17:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reidmit.com/writing/a-new-website/</guid><description>Welcome to my new website!
After several years of designing and redesigning, building and rebuilding, deleting and recreating my personal website an absurd number of times (30?), all without ever putting any real content on it, I have decided that enough is enough. I&amp;rsquo;m settling on a simple design and an easy-to-use framework for building the site (more on that in this post!), so I can focus on what should really be the most important thing: the content.</description></item><item><title>Pixers</title><link>https://reidmit.com/projects/pixers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reidmit.com/projects/pixers/</guid><description>Pixers is a tool for creating generative art, pixel-by-pixel. You define a few parameters (color palette, number of pixers, etc.) and let the pixers draw you a picture. Even when using the same settings, no two pixer drawings are alike. Try it out!
Here&amp;rsquo;s how I described it when I first made it:
Pixers are tiny (1px by 1px) creatures. They move completely randomly. To start, each pixer is randomly assigned a color from the chosen color palette.</description></item><item><title>Hashtag Lonely</title><link>https://reidmit.com/projects/hashtag-lonely/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reidmit.com/projects/hashtag-lonely/</guid><description>I built a robot that complains on Twitter until you pay attention to it. When you do, it takes your picture and posts it to Twitter. But after this brief moment of happiness, it&amp;rsquo;s back to complaining again.
The robot is powered by an Arduino running some Processing code that uses OpenCV for face detection and the Twitter API for posting online.
This was my final project for a class called Robotics, Digital Media, &amp;amp; the Environment.</description></item><item><title>Handmade Film</title><link>https://reidmit.com/projects/handmade-film/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reidmit.com/projects/handmade-film/</guid><description>These three videos were made on Super 8mm film and hand-developed/hand-scratched/hand-colored. I made them for a class called Handmade Film, in which we were encouraged to experiment with different ways to intervene upon the film before and after developing it.
The process involved shooting some footage, developing it in a darkroom, cutting/rearranging/scratching the film strips, digitizing the footage with a telecine machine, and then doing final editing and sound design with Adobe Premiere.</description></item><item><title>Wounded Sky</title><link>https://reidmit.com/projects/wounded-sky/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reidmit.com/projects/wounded-sky/</guid><description>I made this music video for Ruby Reilly&amp;rsquo;s original song &amp;ldquo;Wounded Sky.&amp;rdquo; Check out more of Ruby&amp;rsquo;s music here.
Ruby is from my hometown. I was home from college for Christmas break, I had recently acquired a Super 8mm film camera from a garage sale, and I loved Ruby&amp;rsquo;s music. I felt this song especially could fit with the analog film aesthetic, so we set out to make this video happen.</description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://reidmit.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reidmit.com/about/</guid><description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Reid! I’m a software engineer, filmmaker, and UX designer currently living in San Francisco. I’m passionate about education, accessibility, and building experiences that make people&amp;rsquo;s lives a little easier or a little more enjoyable. My pronouns are he/him/his.
These days, I’m especially interested in front-end web development (JavaScript, React, etc), building accessible user interfaces, and programming language design (compiler-writing, type-checking, etc).
Prior to entering the real world, I grew up in a suburb of New York and went to school at Pomona College, where I majored in computer science and film.</description></item></channel></rss>