<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Reid Mitchell</title>
    <link>http://reidmitchell.net/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Reid Mitchell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 17:19:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://reidmitchell.net/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing your first webpage, pt. 1: HTML</title>
      <link>http://reidmitchell.net/posts/writing-your-first-webpage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 17:19:16 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://reidmitchell.net/posts/writing-your-first-webpage/</guid>
      <description>So, you want to build a website, but you don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start.
Maybe you&amp;rsquo;ve heard something about HTML, but you aren&amp;rsquo;t sure what it is. Maybe you&amp;rsquo;ve never heard of it. Either way, this post will help you get started building websites!
What is a website? A website is just a bunch of files, like the files on your computer. Each file is made up of some text that tells your browser (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wrapping your head around recursion</title>
      <link>http://reidmitchell.net/posts/wrapping-your-head-around-recursion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 05:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://reidmitchell.net/posts/wrapping-your-head-around-recursion/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s start with an analogy.
Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re standing in a long line of people waiting for something on a very foggy day. It&amp;rsquo;s so foggy that nobody in line can see further than one person ahead of them and one person behind them. You certainly can&amp;rsquo;t see the beginning of the line. But you&amp;rsquo;re growing impatient, so you would like to know your position in the line. Are you 5th or 500th?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I built this site</title>
      <link>http://reidmitchell.net/posts/how-i-built-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 15:21:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://reidmitchell.net/posts/how-i-built-this-site/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m fascinated by the different technologies, languages, and methods people use to build websites. When I see a website I admire, I often spend time digging to see how it was built. So, I wanted to share the details behind how this site is made.
There are tons of great options out there for this kind of thing, all with different strengths: Wordpress, Jekyll, Hexo, to name just a few.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new website (finally!)</title>
      <link>http://reidmitchell.net/posts/a-new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 05:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://reidmitchell.net/posts/a-new-website/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my new website!
After several years of designing and redesigning, building and rebuilding, deleting and recreating my personal website an absurd number of times (30?), all without ever putting any real content on it, I have decided that enough is enough. I&amp;rsquo;m settling on a simple design and an easy-to-use framework for building the site (more on that in this post!), so I can focus on what should really be the most important thing: the content.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>